[女孩] B
[girl] B
B  B
蓝天！
Blue sky!
[女人]天空
[woman] Sky
[呼气] S
[exhales] S
云
Clouds
[女孩] D
[girl] D
D  D
狗！
Dog!
狗？狗在哪里？
Dog? Where's the dog?
[女孩]那边
[girl] Over there
没看到吗
Didn't you see it?
没有
No
那是什么样的狗？
What kind of dog was it?
小狗
Small dog
有趣
Interesting
18岁
E for  E for
象！
elephant!
[女孩]大象？哪里？
[girl] Elephant? Where?
是的什么，你错过了吗？
Yeah What, did you miss it?
[笑]
[laughs]
嘿亲爱的不要挑pick子来吧
Hey, sweetie Don't pick at your scab Come on
我只是在检查
I was just checking
你打了那个洞吗？
Did you make that hole?
已经是那样了
It was already like that
会留下疤痕
It'll leave a scar
如果莉莉·史蒂文斯（Lily Stevens）不推我，我什至不会a
I wouldn't even have a scab if Lily Stevens didn't push me
如果您不向她扔粉笔，莉莉·史蒂文斯（Lily Stevens）就不会推您
Lily Stevens wouldn't have pushed you if you hadn't thrown chalk at her
她在对我做鬼脸
She was making faces at me
[女人]我们不伤害别人
[woman] We don't hurt people
永远不会
Not ever
她理应受到伤害
She deserved to be hurt
[喘气]不，她没有
[gasps] No, she didn't
克拉拉，没有人应该受到伤害，
Clara, no one deserves to be hurt,
没有人
no one
好的？
Okay?
来吧
Come on
[女人]都好吗？
[woman] All good?
[克拉拉]是的
[Clara] Yeah
[打开水龙头]
[turns on faucet]
[电台主持人]我去见了TJ他是一个很好的绅士
[radio host] I got to meet TJ He's a nice, nice gentleman
请进入TJ's，在那里自己弄些华夫饼
Please go in to TJ's and get yourselves some waffles there
这就是清单上的内容，我将其列为第二
So that is on the list, and I'm gonna put it down as number two
因为最后-
because last--
[播客中的托尼·罗宾斯]我们成长或死亡
[Tony Robbins on podcast] We grow or we die
因此，我们不知道我们使用事件作为触发
So, we're unaware that we use events as a trigger
回到我们知道的模式
to get home back to the patterns we know
即使不舒服
even if it's uncomfortable
因此，如果您确定自己的住所，
So, if you identify where you live,
在情感上，限制您的模式，
emotionally, the patterns that are limiting you,
-第二件是找到解毒剂 -[电话铃声]
-the second piece is find the antidote -[phone dings]
-拉屎 -[Robbins]我们都会面对，
-Shit -[Robbins] We all will face,
一生中多次遭受极端压力
multiple times in our life, extreme stress
人们生活的不同不是我们面对的，
The difference in peoples' lives is not what we face,
这就是我们面对的事情
it's what we do with what we face
生活给了我们这些事件，这些就是“可怕的事件”
Life gives us these events, these, quote, "horrific events,"
因为我们生活中的某个领域必须发展
because there's an area of our life that has to grow
你可以带自己去一个地方
You can take yourself from a place
面对绝对的悲剧，
where in the face of absolute total tragedy,
你胜利了
you triumph
[温柔地]你一定是在跟我开玩笑
[softly] You've gotta be kidding me
[轮胎爆裂]
[tire bursts]
妈的 65岁
Oh, shit
[克拉拉，睡意]妈妈
[Clara, sleepily] Mommy
我们为什么停下来？
why did we stop?
[门铃响起]
[door alarm beeping]
[关门]
[door closes]
太棒了
Oh, great
!！
Ow!
妈妈，我们在哪里？
Where are we, Mommy?
某个地方，亲爱的
Somewhere, sweetie
[克拉拉哼唱]
[Clara humming]
[女人]你知道吗，罂粟教我如何换轮胎
[woman] You know, Poppy taught me how to change a tire
有一天我会教你
One day I'll teach you
同时，您可能应该过来这里
In the meantime, you should probably come over here and
抢先一步并注意
get a head start and pay attention
[克拉拉]不，这很无聊
[Clara] Nah, that's boring
[叹气]
[sighs]
是的，适合自己
Yeah, suit yourself
也许你可以帮忙
Maybe you can help
给妈妈买咖啡
by getting Mommy her coffee
[呼气]
[exhales]
来吧
Come on
[咕unt声]
[grunts]
-[克拉拉]妈妈-[叹气]哦，天哪
-[Clara] Mommy -[sighs] Oh, God
[轻轻]哦，天哪
[softly] Oh, God
[克拉拉]我们到俄克拉荷马州时，可以
[Clara] When we get to Oklahoma, can we
[克拉拉尖叫]
[Clara screaming]
克拉拉
Clara?
[尖叫继续]
[screaming continues]
[哭]
[crying]
-给我看看！ -妈妈，它咬了我！
-Show me! -Mommy, it bit me!
让我看看，克拉拉
Let me see, Clara
[克拉拉哀号]
[Clara wails]
天啊
Oh, God
好的没关系，亲爱的
Okay It's okay, sweetie
没关系没关系
It's okay It's okay
[克拉拉继续哭泣]
[Clara continues wailing]
[叹气]
[sighs]
好啦好啦
Come on, come on
哦，没关系克拉拉克拉拉
Oh, it's okay Clara? Clara?
来吧宝贝
Come on, baby
哦亲爱的
Oh, sweetie
[喘气]
[panting]
[在电唱机上播放的“月圆”
["Moon Dawging" playing on record player]
[克拉拉呜呜声]
[Clara whimpers]
等等，亲爱的
Hold on, sweetie
[女人]你好？
[woman] Hello?
你好？
Hello?
有人在家吗？
Is anybody home?
你好？
Hello?
来吧，和我在一起，宝贝，好吗？
Come on, stay with me, baby, okay?
宝贝，跟我在一起
Just stay with me, baby
跟我在一起
Stay with me
天啊好啦好啦
Oh, God Come on, come on
[沉重地呼吸]
[breathing heavily]
很抱歉插手
I'm so sorry for barging in
我的小女孩，她被蛇咬了，
My little girl, she got bitten by a snake,
我真的需要你的帮助
and I really need your help
我漏气了，无法发出信号
I got a flat tire, and I can't get a signal
她真的很生气我不知道该怎么办
She's really burning up I don't know what to do
亲爱的，你真幸运
You're in luck, darlin'
我在这里做了很多工作我帮她
I've worked on many a bite out here Let me help her
哦，感谢上帝
Oh, thank God
哦，她要蓝了她要蓝了！ -给我
-Oh, she's going blue She's going blue! -Here, let me
请帮助她！
Please help her!
你能做什么？
What can you do?
最近的城镇图里亚（Tulia）
The nearest town's Tulia
您会在那儿找到医院
You'll find a hospital there
您最好将轮胎整理好
You best get that tire sorted out
来吧，亲爱的，不要只是站在那里时间太浪费了
Come on, don't just stand there, honey Time's a-wasting
稍后我们将讨论付款
We'll discuss payment later
没关系，亲爱的
It's okay, sweetie
[紧张]
[straining]
[咕unt声]
[grunts]
妈在这里
Mommy's here
克拉拉
Clara?
Clara
妈妈
Mommy
[松一口气]
[sighs in relief]
[咕unt声]
[grunts]
[“月牙儿”继续播放]
["Moon Dawging" continues playing]
[轻轻]好吧来吧亲爱的
[softly] Okay Come on, sweetie
[男人]我们将把她整日待在家里，监视她的状况，
[man] We'll keep her in for the day, monitor her condition,
但是请相信我，如果一个五岁的孩子被响尾蛇咬伤……
but trust me, if a five-year-old was bitten by a rattlesnake
（笑）你会知道的
[chuckles] you'd know it
从外观上看，只是疲惫，轻度脱水
From the looks, it's just exhaustion, mild dehydration
你应该见过她的她正在燃烧，没有呼吸
You should've seen her She was burning up, she wasn't breathing
为了基督，她变成了蓝色
She turned blue, for Christ sakes
[医生]在开车过程中，您是否感觉完全不适？
[doctor] Were you feeling out of sorts at all during the drive?
[女人]没有
[woman] No
-[医生]服药？你拿什么吗-[女人]没事，没事
-[doctor] Medication? You taking anything? -[woman] Nothing, no
听着，凤凰城到俄克拉荷马州的旅程可能很长
Listen, Phoenix to Oklahoma can be a long haul
是的，我不是一个很好的飞行者，
Yeah, well, I'm not a very good flier,
所以开车是两种邪恶中的较小者
so driving was the lesser of two evils
[医生]你感觉
[doctor] Were you feeling, uh
这有必要吗？
Is this necessary?
令人担忧或
apprehensive or
开车前有压力吗？
stressed before the drive?
嗯
Uh
不，是的，我想
No Uh, yes, I guess
太疯狂了嗯
It's been pretty crazy Um
我们从头开始，
We're starting over,
而克拉拉（Clara）的举动很多
and the move's been a lot on Clara
你是单身母亲吗？
You're a single mother?
是
Yes
[医生]稍微抬高不足为奇，但没有令人震惊
[doctor] Slightly elevated Not surprising, but nothing alarming
看，我知道这听起来很疯狂
Look, I know this sounds crazy
但是必须有某种解释
But there has to be some kind of explanation
我的意思是那个老女人，也许她有
I mean, that old woman, maybe she had
我不知道，就像她架子上的某种古老疗法一样
I don't know, like an ancient remedy on her shelf or something
我只是
I'm just
我只是告诉你发生了什么
I'm just telling you what happened
[医生]你女儿会没事的
[doctor] Your daughter's gonna be fine
她只需要休息
She just needs to rest
您需要做同样的事情
You need to do the same
去睡一会
Get some sleep
[男人]就是这样
[man] That's all it is
上帝的旨意
God's will
[sobs]我知道
[sobs] I know
[嗅]
[sniffles]
[小伙子]真是太小了
[man] Such a pretty little thing
认为我们差点失去了她
To think we almost lost her
你真幸运事情可能以截然不同的方式结束
You really are lucky Things could have ended much differently
你是？
You are?
我在这里谈论您的付款，里奇韦女士
I'm here to talk about your payment, Ms Ridgeway
哦
Oh
你为什么不拉椅子？
Why don't you pull up a chair?
所以，我和我女儿都有保险
So, we have insurance, my daughter and I, both
我们都被覆盖
We're both covered
哦，我不是在说你的医院债务
Oh, I'm not talking about your hospital debt
我说的是其他债务
I'm talking about the other debt
您现在欠的那个
The one you now owe
为你女儿做的事情并不便宜
What was done for your daughter doesn't come cheap
她的小灵魂得以幸免
Her little soul was spared
现在您欠一个
And now you owe one in return
[笑]
[laughs]
对不起，我以为你说了灵魂
I'm sorry, I thought you said soul
里奇韦女士，您没多久还清债务
Ms Ridgeway, you don't have long to pay your debt
您只有直到日落，这是
You only have until sunset, which is
现在只
now only
七个小时的路程
seven hours away
您所选择的灵魂可以是您选择的任何一个，
The soul you take can be any one of your choosing,
但必须是人类
but it must be human
而且必须按时足额支付
And it must be paid in full and on time
好的我
Okay, I
不太了解发生了什么
don't really understand what's going on
我不知道你是谁
I don't know who you are
我想我叫安全性
I think I'm gonna call security
我希望你离开房间，让我的女儿独自一人
I would like you to leave the room, leave my daughter alone
里奇韦女士未能偿还债务，
Failure to meet your debt, Ms Ridgeway,
会导致您女儿的病情恢复原状
will result in your daughter's condition returning to what it was
我希望你现在离开
I'd like you to leave now
让我提醒你那会是什么样子
Let me, uh, remind you of what that'd look like
[克拉拉呜呜声]
[Clara whimpers]
克拉拉克拉拉
Clara? Clara?
-Sweetie？她会受苦的
-Sweetie? -She will suffer
你对她做了什么？
What've you done to her?
在她屈服于蛇毒之前
before she succumbs to the snake venom
通过她的小身体工作
working its way through her tiny body
不，请停止
No, please, stop it
里奇韦女士，她会死的，我可以向你保证
She will die, Ms Ridgeway, that I can assure you
让它停下来！他妈的滚开！出去！
Make it stop! Fucking get out of here! Get out!
救命！现在有人来这里！
Help! Someone come in here, now!
拜托，有人帮我！
Please, somebody help me!
[人]七个小时，里奇韦女士
[man] Seven hours, Ms Ridgeway
[警报声]
[alarm blaring]
您最好继续前进
You best get a move on
[克拉拉]妈妈
[Clara] Mommy
[克拉拉呜呜声]
[Clara whimpers]
[女人]我需要帮助！在这里！
[woman] I need help! In here!
快点，拜托！
Quick, please!
天啊！
Oh, God!
好吧，我需要你打电话
Okay, I need you to call--
-[女护士]这里有事吗？ -[警报停止]
-[female nurse] Did something happen here? -[alarm stops]
-您要我们给谁打电话？ -小姐？
-Who do you want us to call? -Miss?
小姐？
Miss?
-[男护士]我应该给保安打个电话吗？ -不不不不！不，不要
-[male nurse] Should I call security? -No, no, no, no! No, don't
那就没有必要了
That won't be necessary
[女护士]你还好吗？
[female nurse] Are you okay?
[沉重地呼吸]
[breathing heavily]
[女士]我从黎明开始就一直在开车
[woman] I've been up since before dawn, driving
也许我需要检查一下马路对面的汽车旅馆
Maybe I need to check into the motel across the road
[女护士]可能是最好的
[female nurse] That's probably for the best
我们会为您照顾她的
We'll keep an eye on her for you
[女人]好的，我就跟她说再见
[woman] Okay, I'll just say goodbye to her
[温柔地]哦，天哪
[softly] Oh, my God
[哭]我不知道发生了什么，克拉拉
[cries] I don't know what's going on, Clara
对不起亲爱的
I'm sorry, sweetie
疯了吧
This is insane
我只希望你一切都好
I just want you to be okay
[电话铃声]
[phone ringing]
[操作员] 9-1-1，您的紧急情况是什么？
[operator] 9-1-1, what's your emergency?
你好？
Hello?
9-1-1，您的紧急情况是什么？
9-1-1, what's your emergency?
[车门关闭]
[car door closes]
[沉重地呼吸]
[breathing heavily]
[车辆驶近]
[vehicle approaching]
大
Great
[吼]我很好！
[yells] I'm fine!
我很好，我不需要任何帮助！
I'm fine, I don't need any help!
她会死的，卡特里娜飓风！
She's gonna die, Katrina!
拯救她的唯一途径！
Only one way to save her!
离我远点
Stay away from me
无处可跑！
There's nowhere to run!
[哭]你离我远点！
[cries] You stay away from me!
[笑]
[laughing]
[嘎嘎作响]
[rattling]
[嘶嘶声]
[hissing]
滚开！
Fuck off!
-[男人继续笑]-[响尾蛇]
-[man continues laughing] -[rattling]
[男人的笑声消失]
[man's laughter fading]
[哭]
[crying]
[沉重地呼吸]
[breathing heavily]
[苍蝇嗡嗡声]
[flies buzzing]
[叹气]
[sighs]
[新闻记者]这是德克萨斯州图里亚的餐厅
[news reporter] This is the diner in Tulia, Texas
47岁的律师唐纳德·科温顿（Donald Covington）在胸部被致命刺伤
where 47-year-old lawyer Donald Covington was fatally stabbed in the chest
在日落之前由32岁的学校老师迈克尔·詹姆斯·华纳（Michael James Warner）
by 32-year-old school teacher Michael James Warner just before sunset
目击者称，华纳一直以一种怪异的方式重复着，
Witnesses say Warner kept repeating, in a bizarre manner,
当他攻击卡温顿时，“以灵魂换灵魂”
"A soul for a soul," as he attacked Covington
华纳目前在美国
Warner is currently in cu--
[卡特里娜飓风]“区别不在于我们所面对的，
[Katrina] "The difference is not what we face,
这是我们面对时选择做的事情”
it's what we choose to do when we face it"
“区别不是我们面对的，
"The difference is not what we face,
这是我们面对时选择做的事情”
it's what we choose to do when we face it"
[呼气]
[exhales]
[心率监测器发出哔哔声]
[heart rate monitor beeping]
[电视上不明显的棒球评论]
[indistinct baseball commentary over TV]
[女人在电视上说话含糊不清]
[woman talking indistinctly on TV]
谢谢
Thank you
喂嗯
Hey, um
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry
大约之前
about before
那
That
那真是我的好管闲事
that was so nosy of me
我不应该只是那样凝视着你的房间
I shouldn't have just been peering into your room like that
没关系
It's fine
不，我只是想表示慰问
No, I just wanted to offer my condolences
他还没走
He's not gone yet
不好了嗯，当然不是
Oh, no Uh Of course not
[深感叹]
[sighs deeply]
-你想坐吗？ -哦，可以，可以
-You wanna sit? -Oh, sure, sure
这样 [清嗓子]
Such a [clears throat]
真奇怪
Such a strange thing
等待爸爸去世
waiting for your daddy to die
[闻]嗯
[sniffles] Um
无论如何，对不起什么风把你吹来？
Anyway, I'm sorry What brings you here?
[呼气]哦，
[exhales] Oh, uh
我的女儿，她中暑了
my daughter, she got sunstroke
我们整天开车，而且
We've been driving all day, and
她感觉不太舒服
she's not feeling too well
[女人]她好吗？
[woman] How's she doing?
她很好嗯
She's fine Um
医生认为她只需要休息一下
Doctor thinks she just needs some rest
嗯，我是萝琳
Um, I'm Loraine
苏珊
Susan
无论如何，嗯，很高兴与您聊天
Anyway, um, it was nice chatting with you
希望您和您的小孩子尽快离开这里
I hope you and your little one get out of here soon
好吧，嗯，实际上她现在很重要
Well, uh, actually she's out for the count right now
我独自一人在那寂静中疯狂起来
and I am going stir-crazy in that silence all by myself
所以我想知道是否可以
So I was wondering if maybe, uh, I could
恩，陪你
uh, keep you company
[罗兰]和爸爸在一起？
[Loraine] With Daddy?
嗯
Mm-hmm
[罗琳]显然，他们能听到您的声音
[Loraine] Apparently, they can hear you
护士形容它像一个
The nurse described it kind of like a
像两面镜或
like a two-way mirror or
还是单向镜？
Or was it a one-way mirror?
无论哪种方式，他都不会醒来
Either way, he won't be waking up
但是我仍然在这里，爸爸
But I'm still here, Daddy
好的，苏珊？
You okay, Susan?
他似乎处于和平状态
He seems to be at peace
是的
Yeah
[深吸]
[inhales deeply]
-[手机震动]-哦，拍
-[cell phone vibrates] -Oh, shoot
嘿，你们都在这里吗？
Hey, y'all here?
B-7
不，是在
No, it's at the, um
好吧，等一下，我来了
All right, just wait there, I'm coming
把它留给我的妹妹在这么小的医院迷路
Leave it to my sister to get lost in a hospital this small
我得去抢他们
I gotta go grab 'em
我应该去买克拉拉
I should go get Clara
-[罗兰]谢谢苏珊 -当然
-[Loraine] Thank you, Susan -Sure
[沉重地呼吸]
[breathing heavily]
[耳语]我必须这样做，我必须这样做
[whispers] I have to do this, I have to do this
我必须这样做，我必须这样做，
I have to do this, I have to do this,
我必须这样做，我必须这样做
I have to do this, I have to do this
[人们接近]
[people approaching]
[水滴]
[water dripping]
[in不清]
[indistinct chatter]
Loraine  Loraine
这是谁？
who is this?
我只是在用浴室
I was just using the, um, bathroom
[心跳监视器警报响起]
[heart rate monitor alarm blaring]
[男人]弗兰克？
[man] Frank?
[女人轻声抽泣]
[women sobbing softly]
[沉重地呼吸]
[breathing heavily]
喔
Oh, f
[尖叫声]
[screams]
[轮胎的尖叫声]
[tires screech]
耶稣基督，夫人！
Jesus Christ, lady!
你没事儿吧？
Are you all right?
-什么到底发生了什么事？ -离我远点
-Wh What the hell happened? -Stay away from me
[司机]你在想什么？
[driver] What were you thinking?
我差点就结束了你！
I almost ended you!
一切都好吗？
Is everything okay?
嘿，你不你看起来不太好
Hey, you don't You don't look all right
看，你要我打电话给别人吗？
Look, you want me to call someone?
让
Let
你他妈的认真吗？
You fucking serious?
嘿!
Hey!
他妈的浴盐，伙计
Fucking bath salts, man
[《我摔成碎片》播放]
["I Fall to Pieces" playing]
♪我摔成碎片♪ ♪ I fall to pieces ♪
♪每次见到你♪ ♪ Each time I see you again ♪
-那个在房子上 -[开门]
-That one's on the house -[door opens]
♪我摔成碎片♪ ♪ I fall to pieces ♪
[酒保]好吧，阿比
[bartender] Well, hell, Abbie
什么，你要把这归结为另一轮路德比受伤，是吗？
What, you gonna put this down to another roller derby injury, huh?
这是您在此处选择的一项运动
It's a heck of a sport you chose there
弗朗辛，请给我一杯啤酒
Just give me a beer, Francine
请？
Please?
[法兰西叹息]
[Francine sighs]
精神错乱的定义
Definition of insanity
在做同样的事情，并期待不同的结果
is doing the same thing and expecting a different result
[阿比]所以他们说
[Abbie]  So they say
我认识你？
I know you?
[开门]
[door opens]
来吧
Come on
够了
Enough's enough
请让我留下一会儿
Let me stay, please, just a little while
阿比，从凳子上站起来
Get up off that stool, Abbie
[Francine] Billy，让她喝完该死的啤酒
[Francine] Billy, just let her finish her damn beer
这与您无关，Francine，除非您当然想要
This don't concern you, Francine, unless, of course, you want it to
[Francine]你们不能在这里全部进入
[Francine] Can't have y'all getting into it here
-艾比-好
-Abbie -All right
好吧
All right
我们走吧
Let's go
[比利]等等
[Billy] Hold up
向弗朗辛（Francine）进场并为此致歉，
Apologize to Francine for coming in here and making a scene,
打扰这个好客户
upsetting this nice customer
继续
Go on
抱歉
Sorry
你们两个都快离开这里吧
Just get out of here, both of y'all
继续前进！
Go on, get!
[开门]
[door opens]
反正地方已经烂了
Place has gone to shit anyways
[Francine]嗯继续
[Francine] Mm-hmm Go on
[开门]
[door opens]
出去出去
Go, get out!
-[关门]-不是吗？
-[door closes] -Ain't they a pair?
他们住在附近吗？
They live near here?
[Francine]哦，是的，Tulia最好的
[Francine] Oh, yeah, Tulia's finest
她最终the告告终只是时间问题
Only a matter of time before she ends up in the obituaries
有些人无能为力
Some people are just beyond help
下车
Get off
[比利]为什么总是要摆个镜头？
[Billy] Why you always gotta make a scene?
上那该死的卡车
Get in that fucking truck
上卡车！
Get in the truck!
我不是站在该死的街道上！
I'm not standing here in the goddamn street!
来吧进来！
Come on Get in!
在！
In!
[货车门关闭]
[truck door closes]
[引擎启动]
[engine starts]
12 Amarosa 12 Amarosa
12 Amarosa
[脚步逼近]
[footsteps approaching]
[人]好吧，继续它不会咬你
[man] Well, go on It ain't gonna bite you
轻巧，易于隐藏，
Lightweight, easily concealable,
但最重要的是:准确
but most important: accurate
通过齐平的弹匣最多可射击16发子弹
Shoots a maximum of 16 rounds through a flush-fitted magazine
我要给你一盒两盒
I'll do you two boxes for the price of one
你曾经，解雇其中之一，亲爱的？
You ever, uh, fire one of those, darlin'?
我要买它
I'll take it
好吧
All right
我只需要看你的执照你是得克萨斯州居民，我接受
I'm just gonna need to see your license You're a Texas resident, I take it
没有
No
好吧，恐怕我不能让你购买枪支
Well, I'm afraid I can't be letting you purchase a firearm
仅德克萨斯州居民
Residents of Texas only
看
Look
我和我女儿，我们曾经
my daughter and I, we were, uh
在路上袭击
attacked on the road
我觉得我需要保护
I feel like I need protection
我不知道您能做什么，但也许您可以
And I don't know what you can do, but maybe you could just
只是视而不见，或者我不
just turn a blind eye, or I don't
[叹气]
[sighs]
什么时候变得像这样？
When did it get to be like this?
我们这个伟大国家的开阔道路是什么时候建成的
When did the open roads of this great country of ours
恢复到这种野蛮？
revert to such savagery?
这是不对的，一点也不
It's not right, not one bit
你的小孩子呢
Where's your little one?
在医院
In the hospital
耶稣什么？
Jesus What?
抱歉，我不能帮您，但是
I'm sorry, I can't help you, but
这个男人可以
this man can
他叫查理住在图里亚
His name's Charlie Lives here in Tulia
你可以在这里找到他
You can find him here
这是一笔纯现金交易
It's a cash-only transaction
我想你会称他为私人经销商
I guess you'd call him a private dealer
[鸣叫]
[chiming]
[嗡嗡声]
[door buzzing]
[男，主讲人]您想要什么？
[man, over speaker] What you want?
你好伯爵，恩，送我了
Hi Earl, uh, sent me
他说他会为我担保
He said he'd vouch for me
你是查理吗？
Are you Charlie?
[查理]丢掉帽子
[Charlie] Lose the cap
[查理含糊地喃喃自语]
[Charlie muttering indistinctly]
好的，卡特里娜·里奇韦（Katrina Ridgeway）
Okay, Katrina Ridgeway
我将不得不做快速身体检查
I'm gonna have to do a quick body check
那真的有必要吗？
Is that really necessary?
好的
Okay
[查理拍拍卡特里娜飓风的腿]
[Charlie patting Katrina's legs]
-你要我给你弄点茶吗？ -不，谢谢
-You want me to fix you up some tea? -No, thank you
更多喝咖啡的人，对吧？
More of a coffee drinker, huh?
我猜
I guess
我的妻子特雷西，她会把橱柜放进去
My wife, Tracy, she'd stock the cupboard
充满了各种异国风味
full of a whole variety of exotic flavors
芙蓉是她的最爱
Hibiscus was her favorite
-那么，我们可以--您确定不想尝试吗？
-So, can we-- -You sure you don't wanna try some?
没关系
It's no trouble
我确定
I'm sure
[口吃]我我得走了
[stammers] I I've gotta go
特雷西不再与我们同在
Tracy is no longer with us
她拿了一桶格洛克，和你要买的那桶一样
She took the barrel of a Glock, identical to the one that you're buying
放在嘴里
and put it in her mouth
好的，我很抱歉
Okay, I am so sorry
很遗憾得知您的妻子，但我得走了
so sorry to hear about your wife, but I've gotta get going
[咯咯笑]
[chuckles]
听我说
Listen to me, just
继续前进
rabbiting on
是的，她是她是你的
Yeah, she's She's all yours
嗯
Uh
一块，就是
The piece, that is
回合又是50回合
The rounds are another 50
我我已经有40岁了
I think I've got 40
我的意思是，我可以沙哑其他十个，但我得走了
I mean, I can rustle up the other ten, but I've gotta go
[叹气]我不会剥夺一个女人拿一块的
[sighs] I ain't gonna deprive a woman of carrying a piece
现在，我将成为什么样的男人？
Now, what kind of a man would I be?
我让那十个滑下来
I'll let the ten slide
谢谢谢谢
Thank you, thank you
您曾经处理过其中之一吗？
You ever handle one of them before?
因为如果您需要一些指示
'Cause if you need some pointers
我免费提供
I offer that for free
不，我
No, I'm, uh
谁是of子的倒霉儿子？
Who's the unlucky son of a bitch?
什么？
What?
他们知道了吗？
They got it coming?
你结束某人
You out to end someone
我可以像平常一样在您的眼睛中看到它
I can see it in your eyes, plain as day
所以，我想知道
So, I wanna know
我想知道，卡特里娜里奇韦（Katrina Ridgeway）
I wanna know, Katrina Ridgeway
你确定
that you're sure
他们得到了它
that they got it coming
[manover video]嗨，格洛克先生，又是我
[manover video] Hi, it's me again, Mr Glock
嗯，我今天想，嗯，我还没有展示过的格洛克斯之一
Uh, I thought today, uh, one of the Glocks I've not demonstrated
或谈论过的，是可靠的老款Glock 19
or talked about, is the good old reliable Glock 19
这是一本装满子弹的杂志，
It's a magazine full of bullets in it,
它在房间里也有一个
and it also has one in the chamber
我会尽快检查
I'll quickly check that
[叹气]
[sighs]
[电话嗡嗡声]
[phone buzzes]
[咕run]
[grunting]
[比利]那他怎么说？
[Billy] So, what'd he say?
[阿比]你是什么意思？
[Abbie] What do you mean?
[比利]他说什么？
[Billy] What'd he say?
-[淋浴房正在运行]-[Abbie]没事
-[shower running] -[Abbie] Nothing
[比利]所以，他什么也没说？
[Billy] So, he said nothing?
[艾比]比利，我低着头，打发时间，
[Abbie] Billy, I kept my head down, clocked off,
然后发誓，我发誓
and got the fuck out of there, I swear
[比利]嗯
[Billy] Hmm
如果你这么说
If you say so
拉屎毛巾都湿了
Shit The towels are all wet
[阿比]哦，我上班之前把它们放进去了他们在干燥的地方
[Abbie] Oh, I put them in before work They're in the drier
-[比利]我去拿 -[艾比]你确定吗？
-[Billy] I'll get 'em -[Abbie] You sure?
[比利]我的女孩不能没有湿毛巾擦干
[Billy] Can't have my girl drying off with no wet towel
这里
Here
[比利]我们要在7:00离开
[Billy] We gotta leave at 7:00
[艾比]好吧
[Abbie] Okay
[比利]我们在那吃饭吗？
[Billy] We'll eat there?
[阿比]当然
[Abbie] Sure
[比利]嗯
[Billy] Hmm
过来
Come here
你懂
You know
您尚未完成处罚
You haven't finished your punishment yet
[艾比]我感觉不太好
[Abbie] I'm not feeling so good
也许我们可以下雨吗？
Maybe we can rain check?
[比利]嗯
[Billy] Hmm
你今天已经把我当傻瓜
You already made a fool of me once today
[阿比，结结巴巴]请
[Abbie, stammering] Please
[比利]没有命令，我们是什么？
[Billy] Without order, what are we?
[艾比]好吧好的
[Abbie] Okay Okay
[比利]我们会是什么？
[Billy] What would we be?
[痛苦中gro吟]动物
[groans in pain] Animals
[温柔地]动物
[softly] Animals
你不想成为动物
You don't wanna be an animal
[阿比嗅探]
[Abbie sniffling]
[阿比]不
[Abbie] No
[剧烈呼气]
[exhales sharply]
半小时应该做
Half-hour should do it
来吧
Come on
我说加油！
I said come on!
[呼气]
[exhales]
[解说员在电视上说话含糊不清]
[commentator speaking indistinctly on TV]
[评论员1] Hardy做得好，
[commentator 1] Good job by Hardy,
然后她试图避免威廉姆斯的踢，
and then she tried to avoid the kick of Williams,
但是威廉姆斯能够得分
but Williams was able to score
[评论员2]现在，这些踢是让他们允许威廉姆斯
[commentator 2] Now, what these kicks do is they allow Williams
在哈迪不停止刺戳的情况下进入猛击范围
to get in punching range without Hardy stopping her jab
她想踢
She wants to kick
她处在猛击范围内，她流淌
She's in punching range, and she flows
[评论员1]和威廉姆斯混为一谈
[commentator 1] And Williams mixing up the punches and kicks
当哈迪猛烈地冲拳时！
while Hardy is punching wildly!
吃几个僵硬的手肘
Eats a couple of stiff elbows
精彩的首轮比赛的中点
Mid-point of what has been a fantastic opening round
[评论员2]她很凶恶，出来-
[commentator 2] She's vicious, coming out--
[评论员1]说到恶毒，
[commentator 1] Speaking of vicious,
威廉姆斯和哈代之间的恶性交流！
a vicious exchange here between Williams and Hardy!
[评论员2] Hardy尚未找到自己的舒适区
[commentator 2] Hardy has not found her comfort zone
她有冒犯的念头
She's had flashes of offense
当然她没有想过要放在口袋里
Certainly hasn't been in the pocket, where she wants to be
[评论员1]威廉姆斯的镇定确实令人印象深刻
[commentator 1] Williams' composure really impressive
[阿比喘着粗气]
[Abbie gasps]
你他妈在干什么？让你的笨蛋回到那里！
The fuck you doing? Get your stupid ass back up there!
什么妈的
What the fuck?
他妈的是你吗？
The fuck are you?
[卡特里娜，结结巴巴]拿钥匙
[Katrina, stammering] Take the keys
慢慢来-好的
-Slowly -Okay
好又慢
Nice and slow
[卡特里娜飓风，沉重地呼吸]好吧，嗯
[Katrina, breathing heavily] Okay, um
放下啤酒
Put the beer down
-[比利]好的，我把它放下来了 -好的
-[Billy] Okay, I'm putting it down -Okay
慢慢来
Slowly
-好的 -啤酒倒了
-Okay -Beer's down
好的上楼
Okay Get on the floor
你下来
You get down
好的你呆在那里别动，好吗？
Okay You stay there Don't move, okay?
谢谢
Thank you
好的，起床起床
Okay, get up Get up
-如果您要卡车--刚起床！
-If you want the truck-- -Just get up!
我要你告诉我
I want you to tell me
如何去车库
how to get to the garage
我们可以从房子到车库吗？
Can we get to the garage from the house?
嗯
Mm-hmm
-是吗？嗯
-Yeah? -Mm-hmm
好的
Okay
你要告诉我
You're gonna show me
[卡特里娜飓风]打开灯
[Katrina] Turn on the light
好的下来吧
Okay Let's go, down
[卡特里娜大呼吸]
[Katrina breathing heavily]
我们要去兜风
We're going for a drive
我要你听从我的指示
I want you to follow my directions
我要带你去某个地方
I'm gonna take you somewhere
好的？你只要听我告诉你
Okay? You just listen to what I tell you
因此，上车
So, get in the car
进去吧
Just get in
[哔哔声]
[car beeps]
只是向前看
Just Just look ahead
[沉重地呼吸]
[breathing heavily]
嘿，离开T形路口
Hey, uh, left at the T-junction
-我们去哪？ -就走吧
-Where are we going? -Just make a left
拉过来
Pull over
杀死引擎
Kill the engine
[引擎关闭]
[engine turns off]
缓慢地将钥匙扔回到这里
Toss the keys back here slowly
请
Please
告诉我你想要什么
Just tell me what you want
我可以给你钱
I can get you money
我可以给你任何你想要的东西拜托，告诉我
I can get you anything you want Please, just tell me
下车
Get out of the truck
不，因为如果我这样做，你就会开枪打我
No 'Cause if I do, you'll shoot me
我不是问你，我是在告诉你下车
I'm not asking you, I'm telling you Get out of the truck
[泪流满面]你为什么要杀了我？
[tearfully] Why are you gonna kill me?
告诉我我做了什么，所以请知道
Just tell me what I've done so I know, please
请不要杀了我
Please don't kill me
-别哭了 -请
-Stop crying -Please
我不想死！ -停止别哭了
-I don't wanna die! -Stop Stop crying
我无能为力，因为你会杀了我
I can't help it because you're gonna kill me
[卡特里娜气息]
[Katrina sighs]
看，我需要你团结起来
Look, I need you to hold yourself together
滚出他妈的车，好吗？你听到我了吗？
and get out of the fucking truck, okay? You hear me?
拜托，因为，看，我知道我这一生做过一些事
Please, because, look, I know I've done some fucked up things in this lifetime
好吧，我知道我有
Okay, I know I have
但请您保证，如果您告诉我，我可以解决
But please, if you tell me, I can fix it, I promise
拜托，因为我不想死！
Please, 'cause I don't wanna die!
好吧，听我说，你这屎！我只想要你他妈的卡车
Okay, listen to me, you piece of shit! I just want your fucking truck
[喘气]
[panting]
不，不，不，不，不
No, no, no, no, no
[枪声]
[gunshot]
[喘气]哦，天哪！
[panting] Oh, God!
[大喊]你在哪里，你这片
[yells] Where are you, you piece of sh
[快门声]
[shutter clicks]
-[女人，带有澳大利亚口音] - [快门声]
-[woman, in Australian accent] Well -[shutter clicks]
你给了你最好的机会，凯特
you gave it your best shot, Kat
留在这那很好等一下
Stay there That's good Hold that
[快门声]
[shutter clicks]
真好
Nice
[快门声]
[shutter clicking]
请
Please
必须有另一种方法来纠正这一错误
There has to be another way to put this right
她只是个孩子
She's just a child
拜托，一定要
Please, there has to be
其他方式
some other way
抱歉，凯特
Sorry, Kat
你知道你要做什么
You know what you gotta do
[沉重地呼吸]
[breathing heavily]
[咯咯笑]
[chuckles]
答应我
Promise me
她会没事的
she'll be all right
你答应我
You promise me
如果我这样做
if I do this
会结束
it'll be over
你就别管她了
and you'll leave her alone
[快门声]
[shutter clicks]
公平的公平
Fair's fair
[焦急地呼吸]
[breathing anxiously]
[咕unt声]
[grunts]
[嗅]
[sniffles]
克拉拉
Clara
我想让你知道我是如此的爱你
I want you to know that I love you so, so, so much
从我的心底
from the bottom of my heart
[嗅]然后
[sniffles] And
这些都没有意义，因为它没有任何意义
none of this is gonna makes sense because it doesn't make any sense
[深呼吸]
[breathes deeply]
但是我想让你知道我不想离开你
But I want you to know that I didn't want to leave you
我必须做我必须做
And I had to do I had to do
为了确保您的安全，我必须做我必须做的事情
I had to do what I had to do to keep you safe
我要你记住我
I want you to remember me
让我靠近你的心
And keep me close to your heart
尽你所能
as best as you can
而且，呃，别让我褪色
And, uh, don't let me fade
我那么爱你
I love you so much
亲爱的，我是如此的如此爱你
I love you so, so, so much, sweetie
[咕unt声]
[grunts]
[克拉拉，低语]妈妈
[Clara, whispering] Mommy
[耳语]
[whimpering]
-[男性低沉的声音]-[gro吟]
-[muffled male voice] -[groans]
[男声低沉]
[muffled male voice]
来吧，你这疯子！
Come on, you crazy bitch!
给我他们他妈的钥匙
Give me them fucking keys
现在呢？
Now what, huh?
你想他妈的玩吗？
You wanna fucking play?
你他妈在干什么？
The fuck you doing?
什么妈的
What the fuck?
[gro吟]
[groaning]
[嘎嘎作响]
[rattling]
[比利的尖叫声]
[Billy screams]
-[th]-[Billy gro吟]
-[thud] -[Billy groans]
[嘶嘶声和嘎嘎声]
[hissing and rattling]
[喘气和窒息]
[wheezing and choking]
[耳语]
[whimpering]
[嘎嘎作响]
[rattling]
[咕unt声]
[grunts]
[喘气]
[gasps]
请不
Please, no
请
Please
拜托
Please, just stop
你为什么做这个？
Why are you doing this?
请住手请
Please stop Please
拜托拜托
Please Please
请住手
Please stop
请！
Please!
为什么？
Why?
你为什么做这个？
Why are you doing this?
为什么？
Why?
嘘
Shh
[轻声]可以
[softly] It's all right
一切都快结束了
It'll all be over soon
你疯了，你这个bit子
You're crazy, you fucking bitch
[咳嗽]
[coughing]
你会为此而燃烧
You're gonna burn in hell for this
你该死的烧，你这fuck子
You're gonna fucking burn, you fucking bitch
你会为此而燃烧！你会燃烧的！
You're gonna burn in hell for this! You'll burn!
[咳嗽]
[coughs]
我们拭目以待
We'll see
[gro吟]
[groans]
[深呼吸]
[breathing deeply]
[呼气]
[exhales]
[手机振动]
[phone vibrating]
你好？
Hello?
[医生]你好，里奇韦女士？
[doctor] Hello, Ms Ridgeway?
请讲
Speaking
这是海斯博士我打电话给你的女儿克拉拉
This is Dr Hayes I'm calling about your daughter Clara
我已经尝试了您大约一个小时
I've been trying you for around an hour now
告诉我
Tell me
抱歉？
Sorry?
她怎么样？
How is she?
她很好她起来了，准备出发了
She's fine She's up, ready to go
她想知道你在哪里 [咯咯笑]
She's wondering where you are [chuckles]
我也是
So am I, for that matter
告诉她我要走了
Tell her I'm on my way
我很快就会到那里
I'll be there soon
好吧，会的我确保她能吃点东西
Okay, will do I'll make sure she gets something to eat
谢谢
Thank you
[叹气]
[sighs]
-[克拉拉]妈妈！嘿亲爱的
-[Clara] Mommy! -Hey, sweetie
[克拉拉]他们给了我红色果冻和冰淇淋
[Clara] They gave me red jello and ice cream
哦，他们有，亲爱的？
Ooh, they did, sweetie?
是的，晚餐吃意大利面
Yeah, and spaghetti for dinner
脖子怎么了
What happened to your neck?
哦，我抓了它
Oh, I scratched it
疼吗
Did it hurt?
是的，一点
Yeah, a little
我们什么时候走？我要留在这里吗？
When are we leaving? Do I have to stay in here?
不，我们不我们现在有空
No, we don't We're free to go now
[卡特里娜]是的不，你说得对，妈妈，
[Katrina] Yeah No, you're right, Mom,
我应该打给你，但我只是不想打扰你
I should have called you right back, but I just didn't want to bother you
但是，我们现在正在上路，是的
But we're hitting the road now, yeah
不，你答应，一切都很好
No Promise you, everything is all good
[克拉拉]我们要写什么信？
[Clara] What letter are we up to?
妈妈？
Mommy?
什么亲爱的
What, sweetie?
我们在写什么信？
What letter were we up to?
呃 [呼气]
Uh [exhales]
我不记得了
I can't remember
你决定
You decide
[克拉拉]好的
[Clara] Okay
搭便车，妈妈
Hitchhiker, Mommy
搭便车的H
H for hitchhiker
你看见他了吗，克拉拉？
Did you see him, Clara?
你有看见他吗？
Did you see him?
[克拉拉]是的
[Clara] Yeah
妈妈，你认为他要去哪里？
Where do you think he's going, Mommy?
我不确定，亲爱的
I'm not sure, sweetie
[克拉拉]轮到你了，妈妈我们由我决定
[Clara] Your turn, Mommy We're up to I
妈妈？
Mommy?
快点，妈妈
Come on, Mommy
一世
I
♪接我♪ ♪ Pick me up ♪
当你感到沮丧时 ♪ When you feel low down ♪
♪然后我们去月之夜'绕城而过♪ ♪ And we'll go moon dawgin' Round this town ♪
♪当情况恶化时♪ ♪ When the situation's aggravatin' ♪
♪让自己动起来吧♪ ♪ Get yourself to motivatin' ♪
♪夜晚的灯光很亮，当太阳下山时♪ ♪ Where the lights are bright at night When the sun goes down ♪
♪走吧，月亮宝贝，宝贝♪ ♪ And let's go moon dawgin' , baby ♪
♪Moon dawgin'♪ ♪ Moon dawgin' ♪
♪我们去月亮舞会吧！ ♪ Let's go moon dawgin' Round this town ♪
♪合适的时机♪ ♪ The right time ♪
♪现在听听我在说什么♪ ♪ Now hear what I say ♪
♪哦，这是夜间，因为那是我一天中的时间♪ ♪ Oh, it's nighttime 'Cause that's my time of day ♪
♪我还活着♪ ♪ I come alive ♪
♪五点后不久 ♪ Shortly after five ♪
♪选择一个场景，梦想并计划好我的烦恼♪ ♪ Pick a scene, dream And scheme my trouble away ♪
♪我准备好登月了，宝贝♪ ♪ I'm ready for moon dawgin', baby ♪
♪Moon dawgin'♪ ♪ Moon dawgin' ♪
♪月亮飞舞，当太阳下山时♪ ♪ Moon dawgin' round When the sun goes down ♪
♪嘈杂的人跳舞 ♪ Noisy people dancin' ♪
♪Swingin'，swayin'，dashin'♪ ♪ Swingin', swayin', dashin' ♪
♪和时髦的唐卡一起唱歌♪ ♪ Singin' along with a groovy thang ♪
♪哦，很有趣，很欢笑♪ ♪ Oh, lots of fun and laughter ♪
♪是的，这就是我的追求 ♪Yeah, that's what I'm after ♪
♪我在Moon Dawgin'Lane找到它♪ ♪ And I find it in Moon Dawgin' Lane ♪
♪所以接我♪ ♪ So, pick me up ♪
当你感到沮丧时 ♪ When you feel low down ♪
♪然后我们去月之夜'绕城而过♪ ♪ And we'll go moon dawgin' Round this town ♪
♪我保证♪ ♪ I guarantee ♪
♪你一大礼包♪ ♪ You one fine spree ♪
♪如果你和我一起去月亮，当太阳下山时♪ ♪ If you go moon dawgin' with me When the sun goes down ♪
♪所以，来吧月亮宝贝，宝贝♪ ♪ So, come and go moon dawgin', baby ♪
♪Moon dawgin'♪ ♪ Moon dawgin' ♪
♪让我们在这个小镇上走月亮吧♪ ♪ Let's go moon dawgin' round this town ♪
♪哦，月亮飞舞着，当太阳下山时♪ ♪ Oh, moon dawgin' round When the sun goes down ♪